A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Log Files (Grant and Project Proposals) FA734
Rockefeller Archive Center
- 1995
  - L95-7: Frank Thomas, Council on Foundation, Congratulatory 1995 Awards Letters (Reel L-595, Frame 1236)
  - L95-12: Lipman Hearne, Inc.: Community Development Partnership Strategy, 1995 (Reel L-596, Frame 27)
  - L95-13: Students for Responsible Business: Leadership Development (Roland Anglin, USIA/UP program), 1995 (Reel L-596, Frame 575)
  - L95-20: National Fatherhood Imitative: Support to promote the issue of responsible and committed fatherhood (USIA/UP program), 1995 (Reel L-598, Frame 1568)
    Includes material on Father Fact, Fatherhood Resource Catalog, National Ad Council Project.
  - L95-25: Ford Foundation: Community Development Human Capital, 1995 (Reel L-597, Frame 2587)
    Establishing a Human Capital Program focusing on staff recruitment, leadership development, and training to enable CDCs to serve low and moderate income communities (USIA/UP program).
  - L95-26: National Puerto Rican Coalition, Inc.: Puerto Rican Community Needs in the 21st Century, 1995 (Reel L-584)
  - L95-28: 21st Century Youth Leadership Training Project: National expansion of the 21st Century Youth Leadership Training Project, 1995 (Reel L-597, Frame 2630)
  - L95-29: Ford Foundation: General Background - Funders Collaboratives (Ruth Ramon, USIA/UP program), 1995 (Reel L-595, Frame 8)
    Includes material on Patterns of Cooperation Among Grantmakers, and Resources for Grantmakers.
  - L95-39: Ford Foundation: Writers Corps (USIA/UP program), 1995 (Reel L-595, Frame 1162)
    Includes material on Associated Writing Program, and AmeriCorps.
- 1996
  - L96-1: Ford Foundation: Human Resource Leadership Development (Ruth Roman, USIA/UP program), 1996 (Reel L-594, Frame 1206)
  - L96-2: Ford Foundation: Meetings of Collaboratives, USIA/UP program, 1996 (Reel L-591, Frame 8)
    Includes Community Development Partnership Strategy, 1997 Annual Conference, July 16-19, 1997, Portland, Oregon.
  - L96-3: Ford Foundation: Eastern Europe program-related investment (PRI): Sendomira Venture Capital Fund for Small and Medium Sized Enterprises / GMA Capital Markets Limited, 1996 (Page L-591, Frame 2146)
  - L96-4: National Campaign to Prevent Teen Pregnancy: Prevention of Teen Pregnancy Initiative, 1996 (Reel L-591, Frame 2182)
  - L96-8: State Organization Project: Wider Opportunity for Women (Urban Poverty program), 1996 (Reel L-594, Frame 903)
  - L96-9: Urban Institute: Survey of Families without Children, "Assessing the New Federalism", 1996 (Reel L-594, Frame 1001)
  - L96-10: Intermediate Technology: international Development Policy Work (Rural Poverty and Resources program), 1996 (Reel L-595, Frame 1077)
  - L96-12: Technoserve: Core support and rural growth through business development (ABCD program), 1996 (Reel L-595, Frame 1011)
  - L96-13: Hudson Institute: Support for Welfare Policy Center, 1996 (Reel L-596, Frame 655)
    Includes material on Workforce Two-Thousand (2000).
  - L96-14: Ford Foundation: Philanthropy and Empowerment Zones (Ruth Roman, Urban Poverty program), 1996 (Reel L-596, Frame 686)
  - L96-15: Ford Foundation: Women and Community Development Initiative (Ruth Roman, USIA/UP program), 1996 (Reel L-597, Frame 8)
  - L96-16: United States Environmental Protection Agency: Brownfields '96: A New Environmental Frontier (Ruth Roman, USIA/UP program) (Frame L-596, Frame 1714)
  - L96-17: Ford Foundation: Development Finance, Community Development Finance Institutions (Ruth Roman, USIA/UP program), 1996 (Reel L-597, Frame 1586)
  - L96-18: Ford Foundation: The Arts and Community Development (Ruth Roman, USIA/UP program), 1996 (Reel L-598, Frame 8)
  - L96-19: Ford Foundation: 1996 Conference on Community Resource and Development (Ruth Roman, USIA/UP program) (Reel L-598, Frame 1471)
    Includes material on Neighborhood Funders Group.
  - L96-20: Ford Foundation: Habitat II meeting and follow up (Ruth Roman, USIA/UP program), 1996 (Reel L-598, Frame 1629)
  - L96-21: Ford Foundation: United Way and Ford Foundation Community Building Meeting, 1996 (Reel L-598, Frame 1760)
  - L96-22: Brandeis University: Support for a conference on out-of-school youth, 1996 (Reel L-598, Frame 2076)
  - L96-23: Wisconsin Works Management and Evaluation Project, Foundation Information Meeting, November 15, 1996, University of Wisconsin-Madison (Reel L-598, Frame 2096)
- 1997
  - L97-1: Ford Foundation: Council on Foundations, 1997 (Reel L-597, Frame 2740)
  - L97-2: Ford Foundation: Annual Memberships, 1997 (Reel L-598, Frame 2202)
    Information on Ford Foundation memberships formerly filed in MCA 838-980.
  - L97-3: Ford Foundation: Collaborating for Educational Reform, RFP, 1997 (Reel L-595, Frame 1446)
  - L97-4: Urban Institute: New Federalism Grant, 1997 (Reel L-591, Frame 2389)
  - L97-5: Progressive Policy Institute: Support for project on ABA Statutory Rape, Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH), 1997 (Reel L-594, Frame 603)
  - L97-6: Academy for Educational Development: School-to-Career Preliminary Report, 1997 (Reel L-594, Frame 638)
  - L97-7: United Nations: International Conference on Population and Development (ICPD), Cairo, Egypt, 1993-1997; Approx. 3600 pages (Reel L-592, Frame 8-2901)
  - L97-8: Mathematica Policy Research Inc., Early Head Start, 1997 (Reel L-594, Reel 974)
  - L97-9: STRIVE, East Harlem Employment Services, Inc., Support for planning an employment-training program, 1997 (Reel L-594, Frame 1041)
  - L97-10: Hillard Pouncy, Black/Puerto Rican Collaboration, 1997 (Reel L-596, Frame 8)
  - L97-11: 'New Investment Strategy for Nonprofit Job Placement and Training Providers', Julia Lopez William Ryan, Mitchell Sviridoff, 1997 (Page L-596, Frame 18)
  - L97-12: Center for Youth Development and Education, 1997 (Reel L-596, Frame 507)
  - L97-13: Institute for American Values: Fatherhood Project (Roll L-596, Frame 668)
  - L97-14: International Women's Health Coalition; Columbia University, Young Men's Clinic, 1997 (Reel L-596, Frame 1515)
  - L97-15: DHHS Fathers' Work Group: Implementation of President Clinton's Request to Support the Role of Fathers' in Families, 1997 (Reel L-596, Frame 1695)
  - L97-16: Ford Foundation Worldwide Meeting on Philanthropy, 1997 October 13-17 (Reel L-597, Frame 1192)
  - L97-17: Medicare Rights Center, 1997 (Reel L-597, Frame 2787)
- 1998
  - L98-1: West Haven Project Match Joint Ventures, 'A Community that Works: The West Haven Project Match Initiative', 1998 (Frame L-594, Reel 1131)
  - L98-3: New Orleans Center for Successful Living, Christian Faith Ministries: Community Development, 1998 (Reel L-591, Frame 2079)
  - L98-4: Creation of a New Historical Preservation, 1998 (Reel L-594, Frame 8)
    Includes: Cornerstones, Maryland Historical Trust, National Center for Heritage Development, New York Landmarks Conservancy, Penn Center.
  - L98-5: Mi Casa Resource Center for Women, Inc.: Latina women and youth services programs (Reel L-594, Frame 730)
  - L98-7: Santa Cruz Barrios Unidos: Building National Coalition of Barrios Unidos, 1998 (Reel L-594, Frame 884)
  - L98-8: Ford Foundation: Support for Youth Development (Ruth Roman, Urban Poverty program), 1998 (Reel L-594, Frame 995)
  - L98-9: Save the Children: Initiate a Youth as Stakeholders Program, 1998 (Reel L-594, Frame 1084)
- 1999
  - L99-2: New York Foundation, Youth Organizing briefing, 1999 (Reel L-591, Reel 1818)
- 2000
  - L00-1: Ford Foundation: Children Youth and Families Learning Group Initiative (ABCD/HDRH program), 2000 (Reel L-594, Frame 1515)